degica.com 2019-03-09

# Degica | Making Japan simple

Last updated: October 12, 2018 

We (DEGICA Co., Ltd.) may collect your personal information in order to provide our services, including EC sites operation, digital content sales and international promotion support. We fully understand the importance of safeguarding your privacy and endeavor to handle your personal information appropriately so that you can do business with us with peace of mind. To this end, we publish our Privacy Policy here. 

## 1\. Scope

This Privacy Policy shall apply to all personal information you provide to us via our websites, phone, email, or in writing, etc., in connection with all of our services. If provisions differing with this Privacy Policy are specified when providing personal information, such provisions shall apply preferentially. Additionally, our Privacy Policy does not apply to personal information obtained separately by advertisers that place advertisements on our websites. 

## 2\. The Information We Collect

To achieve the purposes of use prescribed in “3. Use and Retention of Your Information”, we shall collect from you the personal information prescribed below. We take efforts to collect the minimum personal information necessary. 

## 2.1 Information Provided by You

  * Your personal information such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, your company name, email address, etc.
  * Login information such as account name (user ID) and password
  * Information regarding payment methods such as credit cards, bank accounts, electronic money, etc.
  * Information for identity verification such as copies of drivers licenses, health insurance cards, etc.

## 2.2 Information Acquired via Cookies

When you visit our websites, we may place a small text file called a “cookie” on your device. You can disable cookies by changing their browser’s settings, but this may result in being unable to use some features provided by the website. 

  * IP address
  * Referring URL (address of the webpage linked from)
  * Device information (browser type and version, time zone settings, operating system, etc.)
  * Information on products and services displayed or searched

## 3\. Use and Retention of Your Information

We use your information for the purposes specified below. We shall not use it for any other purposes than below. 

  * To enable logging in to your account, forums, message boards, etc.
  * To ship our products or gift and to provide our services such as downloads, etc.
  * To bill fees for providing our services
  * To refund when service cancellation
  * To transfer collected fee on behalf of contractor of our service
  * To reply appropriately to your inquiries about our service
  * To send you information and advertisements such as direct mailings or email newsletters, etc.
  * To notify you of updates, changes, or discontinuation, etc., of our services.
  * To improve existing services and conduct R&D for the development of new services
  * To utilize information for services such as analysis, marketing, and information dissemination, etc., as statistical data in which individuals or corporations are anonymized
  * To perform identity verification
  * To prevent, investigate, and identify fraud, cyber-attacks, and other illegal activities or violations of our services’ terms of use, and to protect our legal rights
  * To utilize information for personnel recruitment

We may retain information about you for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the purposes described above. In order to secure your information, we take all the security measures described in “6. Security” 

## 4\. Sharing and Provision of Your Information

We shall not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. However, we may share your information with our partners or provide it to a third party in the following circumstances. 

  * When you have provided consent in advance
  * When necessary for our partners to perform outsourced duties (transmitting email, processing payments, etc.)
  * When necessary to provide statistical data in which individuals or corporations are anonymized
  * When necessary to sell our business in whole or in part
  * When required by law
  * Cases of urgent necessity in which there is imminent danger to the life, body, or property of an individual, and in which it is difficult to obtain the consent of the person
  * Cases of cooperation with legal demands by public institutions such as judiciary agencies or the police, etc.
  * Cases in which there is reasonable suspicion that the individual has violated the law or our terms of use in connection with the use of our services, and it has been recognized as necessary to protect our or third party’s rights, assets, or services, etc.

## 5\. Your Rights

When we receive your request of disclosure, correction, amendment, deletion, erasing, suspension of use, or notification of the purposes of use of your information, we shall take care of it promptly within a reasonable scope. Under the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation), those residing in the European Economic Area (EEA) countries have the rights to revoke consent to provide personal information, to raise objections regarding the handling of personal information, and to file complaints with the competent supervisory authorities. 

## 6\. Security

To prevent unauthorized access or leaking of your personal information, and maintain the accuracy of information and dispose of it properly, we shall comply with all applicable laws, and make efforts to handle personal information with high level of security. In order to protect your privacy and ensure security, your information shall be protected by passwords. Additionally, we shall use industry standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions when necessary. When we outsource duties to a third party for the purpose of providing services to you, a contract will be signed to ensure proper management of the outsourcer. We shall conduct regular reviews to confirm that these activities are being properly performed and at a suitable level. 

## 7\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may revise our Privacy Policy in whole or in part. In the event of revisions, they shall apply automatically at the point in time they are posted on our websites or when we notify you of them. 

## 8\. Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the contents of this Privacy Policy or other aspects of how your personal information is handled, please contact us below.   
DEGICA Co., Ltd. / Personal information protection manager  
PHONE: +81-50-6861-0240  
e-mail: info@degica.com  
Reception hours: 10:00am to 5:00pm, Monday to Friday (except Japan’s public holidays, the Year-End and New Year holidays)
